// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
     question:"Where does The Elephant Gathering (billed as one of the world's greatest animal spectacles) occur every year? ",
        answer: "Minneriya National Park",
        options: [
          "Yala National Park",
          "Minneriya National Park",
          "Udawalawe National Park",
          "Wilpattu National Park"
]
  },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A word used in Sri Lanka to greet someone. What is this traditional Sri Lankan greeting?",
    answer: "Ayubowan ",
    options: [
      "Jumbo",
      "Ayubowan ",
      "Bohoma Isthuthi ",
      "Takahiri"
]
  },

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is central highland’s UNESCO world heritage site in Sri Lanka? ",
    answer: "Yala National Park ",
    options: [
      "Lion Rock Sigiriya ",
      "Dambulla Cave Temple ",
      "Yala National Park ",
      "Horton Plains Nuwara Eliya "
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the best National Park for bird watching in Sri Lanka bordering the island’s eastern coast? ",
    answer: "Udawalawa National Park",
    options: [
      "Yala National Park",
      "Udawalawa National Park",
      "Kumana National Park",
      "Wilpattu National Park"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Expand UNWTO?",
    answer: "United Nations World Tourism Organization",
    options: [
      "United Nations World Tourism Organization",
      "United Nations Wide Tourism Organization",
      "United Nations World Trade Organization",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When is World Tourism Day?",
    answer: "September 27",
    options: [
      "June 5",
      "November 20",
      "April 1",
      "September 27"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A hipster-chic east coast village known for its surfing spots that attract surfers from around the world. What is it?",
    answer: "Arugam Bay",
    options: [
      "Nilaveli Beach",
      "Arugam Bay",
      "Marble Beach",
      "Kalkudah Beach"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In which Sri Lankan province is the famous Temple of the Tooth located?",
    answer: "Central province ",
    options: [
      "Central province ",
      "Southern province ",
      "North province ",
      "Uva province "
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What makes the Golden Temple of Dambulla so unusual?",
    answer: "It is built in a cave",
    options: [
      "It is built on a rock",
      "It is built in a cave",
      "It is built on a wood",
      "It is built on a cement"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which Sri Lankan city is the Esala Perahera festival held? ",
    answer: "Kandy",
    options: [
      "Colombo",
      "Kataragama",
      "Kelaniya",
      "Kandy"
    ]
  },

];